## FELIX CARVAJAL

#### SKILLS

Knowledge in computer science and programming. I have experience in the area of web, desktop and mobile application development in frameworks like: Angular 2+, Javascript/TypeScript, C# (ASP.NET, .Net Core, .Net, Xamarin), Java EE (Spring, Hibernate), PHP (Laravel), Flutter, NativeScript. and Methodologies and flow works like: Agile, Scrum, TDD, DDD, S.O.L.I.D., KISS, DRY.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Concentra SRL, Santo Domingo- Software Developer

Sep 2018 - April 2019

- Backend C# ASP.NET MVC.
- Frontend Angular 6.
- DB MSSQL.

#### BM Cargo, Santo Domingo — Software Developer

Oct 2019 - Feb 2020

- Programador aplicaciones móviles en NativeScript.
- Programación backend API en C# (ASP.NET, Windows Forms, WPF).
- Programación Frontend Angular 7/8

# Blue Coding LLC, EE.UU. (Miami, Florida) — Cross-platform Mobile Developer

Oct 2020 - Feb 2021 (Proyecto Temporal)

Programación Móvil Javascript (NativeScript-vue)

#### **Utreee, Santo Domingo** — Software Developer

Feb 2021 - Feb 2022

- Java EE (Spring, Tomcat, Java Android)
- PHP, Javascript, MySQL, Cordova Framework 7

#### Wepsys, Santo Domingo - FullStack Developer

Febrero 2022

- BackEnd (.Net 6, SQL Server, Docker)
- FrontEnd (Angular 12, Razor, React)
- Jira
- Github

### **EDUCACIÓN**

**Universidad Autónoma de Santo Domingo** — *Computer Sciense Degree*Agosto 2013

Conin/Infosyp - Development in C# (ASP.NET)
June 2016 - February 2017

Online Courses — Ruby, Ruby on Rails, Flutter, Xamarin, PHP (Laravel), ReactNative, Figma/AdobeXD, Android Kotlin,